[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_Lochnir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_01_SpeakLochnir_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Fortuitous Times",
        "Description": "Ser Payne Bennett has requested you to meet the Minister of Monarch's Bluffs in his office.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's so fortuitous?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Why, we have just learned the True Heir to the throne is returning to the region! \\n\\nThis is a day we have been awaiting for centuries, and a sign of new hope even during these troublesome times.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Minister Lochnir has been managing affairs in this town longer than most of us have been here. \\n\\nHe's someone you simply must meet. Don't dally, now!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well now, two new faces to Prydwen in one day - many a year since I've seen that. But these are special times. \\n\\nAfter centuries, the True Heir returns, and the royal bloodline will once again sit upon the throne.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "A Prydwen Tradition",
        "Description": "Minister Lochnir has generously arranged a room for you at Demetrius Biton's inn. Check in and warm yourself by the fire.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"When does Ser Gawain arrive?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Only a matter of days. I am personally attending to preparations even now, as is my duty. \\n\\nTradition is everything, wouldn't you say? One such custom I've established is that we offer our guests a complementary room at the inn.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The hour of the True Heir's return approaches quickly, and I have much to do. \\n\\nYou are welcome at the inn.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Now there's a familiar face! About time you caught up. \\n\\nHere we find ourselves in a little village pulled straight from the Middle Ages. Is it me, or does nothing on this island make any sense at all?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "With Good Grace",
        "Description": "Grace O'Malley has given you the coin she owes you. Look for bargains at the Trading Post and store the excess at the Storage Shed.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So what do we do now?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, you got that coin I just gave you so I'd suggest you get to spending it. \\n\\nBuy yourself a new blade, some new boots, whatever suits your fancy.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You're in a new town, and you have some coin now - I'd get to spending it or stashing it myself. \\n\\nCarrying it around town, you're just asking for someone to slip a hand in your pocket and steal it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Look at you! Here just a few hours and you're already the most popular person in town. You had a caller while you were out. \\n\\nThat overly chipper knight from the town gate dropped by, says he wants to have a word with you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Honor and Loss",
        "Description": "Grace O'Malley has asked you to meet with Ser Payne, the friendly knight you met at the gate to Monarch's Bluffs.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of trouble?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Sounds like some kinda plague - people turning on their friends and neighbors with cold murder in their eyes. \\n\\nUnlike those red-eyed bastards on the beach, these folks aren't possessed. Seems like they don't have any souls at all.",
        "InProgressResponse": "One of the fellas in the tavern told me Ser Payne's two hundred years old! \\n\\nIt's going to take me a while to get used to this place.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Come in, and be welcome. I will never forget the way this island tested me when I first arrived. \\n\\nI strive to ensure we are patient with newcomers, and in these times, our customs are even more difficult to observe.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_AllyaMusa",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "The Pride of Prydwen",
        "Description": "Knight-Regent Jin Jae, knight in charge of Monarch's Bluffs, has asked you to help Allya Musa at Cynefin Mines.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What have you done for them?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "We offer shelter, comfort, and we dispatched knights to secure the roads, but many never returned. \\n\\nMinister Lochnir counsels patience. He believes the royal bloodline will solve all problems. But I feel I must act.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Foreman Allya usually sends regular status reports. \\n\\nI hope all is well, but we need to be certain.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Whoah, you. If you thought you were going to the mines, think again. \\n\\nIf you have loved ones in there, I don't know what to tell you. Most everyone's fallen Lost, and no support from Prydwen in sight.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_EliasDerit",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Crisis at the Mines",
        "Description": "A worried Allya Musa wants you to rescue any surviving miners at Cynefin Mine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can go in and search.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You're brave, I'll give you that. But we're not talking about a handful of Withered, we're talking about the whole damn mine. \\n\\nIf you go in there and find anyone, I'd get them out of there fast.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You may not be a knight, but you got courage. \\n\\nAnd if that translates into some of my miners getting out of there, I sure as hell won't complain.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Finally, a sign of hope! A brave warrior battling their way through the Withered. \\n\\nIt's beyond a relief to see you up here. Now maybe we can find a way to reclaim the mine.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_EliasDerit",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "A Most Mysterious Tablet",
        "Description": "Elias Derit believes the strange magical tablet is causing the trouble at the mines. Destroy the tablet and the Lost Pirates who guard it.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Someone planted the tablet?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm sure of it! The damn thing was making some unearthly sound. Not a one of us would touch it. \\n\\nThe next day, we had Lost pirates jumping down from the rocks, and then everyone started falling Lost.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You said you'd shatter that damn tablet, and I'll be holding you to it!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "God's blood! I didn't think you could actually pull it off, but you did! \\n\\nThough it seems my hope of the Lost leaving the mine won't be happening anytime soon.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Fragments of Truth",
        "Description": "Elias Derit wants you to take back news of Hiraeth Peak to Knight-Regent Jin Jae at Prydwen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Alright. Ready when you are.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You did all the work, so I'll let you have the honor of bringing whatever remains of that tablet back to Prydwen. \\n\\nThere's sages and people of that sort who can make sense of them. Oh. Ask the Knight-Regent, she'll know.",
        "InProgressResponse": "A deal's a deal. \\n\\nYou said you'd take whatever's left of that tablet back to Prydwen. So get to it, then.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I'm glad to see you've returned safely. Not long after you departed, I finally heard the news. \\n\\nTell me though, is it as bad as they say? Surely some of the miners made it out?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Friend or Foe",
        "Description": "Knight-Regent Jin Jae suspects Minister Lochnir of evil doings. Interrogate him and discover the truth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There was a mysterious tablet. I have fragments.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A mysterious tablet, in the mines? Hm... These fragments appear to be Ancient in origin. I'm no expert, but I will consult the sage, Younge Geiser. \\n\\nIn the meantime, I need to know how the mine fell without my knowledge.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I can't think of any reasonable explanation why Lochnir would keep the Foreman's missives from me. \\n\\nI am anxious to hear what he has to say.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You return, but without Minister Lochnir. I assume he claimed he was too busy with his preparations? \\n\\nPerhaps it's just as well. As Knight-Regent, it may be best if I handle matters personally going forward.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success_alt",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Friend or Foe",
        "Description": "Knight-Regent Jin Jae suspects Minister Lochnir of evil doings. Interrogate him and discover the truth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There was a mysterious tablet. I have fragments.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A mysterious tablet, in the mines? Hm... These fragments appear to be Ancient in origin. I'm no expert, but I will consult the sage, Younge Geiser. \\n\\nIn the meantime, I need to know how the mine fell without my knowledge.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I can't think of any reasonable explanation why Lochnir would keep the Foreman's missives from me. \\n\\nI am anxious to hear what he has to say.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You return, but without Minister Lochnir. I assume he claimed he was too busy with his preparations? \\n\\nPerhaps it's just as well. As Knight-Regent, it may be best if I handle matters personally going forward.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 10,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Knight in the North",
        "Description": "Knight-Regent Jin Jae is beginning to trust you. She's asked you to support Ser Payne Bennett's war efforts at Brysedd Shore.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, I fought them myself.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "These pirates could only have come from the Brysedd Shore to the north. There was a den of brigands there, and now they are apparently Lost. \\n\\nThis seems to be an alarming trend, and we must find the source of it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Look for Ser Payne and his squire at Brysedd Shore. I have a sense they will need your support.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, you're back!  I'm at a bit of a loss here. A few months ago, this barren beach had nothing but a smattering of pirates. \\n\\nNow it appears to be a war camp, with more pirates and supplies arriving by the minute.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 11,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Brigands on the Beach",
        "Description": "Ser Payne has asked you to use unusual methods to fight the filthy Lost pirates. Cut off their supplies and set their boats adrift!",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You think they'll honor that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh, well, yes, good point. I suppose then we have a more limited set of options. \\n\\nI'm afraid I'm not much of a strategist in a scenario like this. What do you think would be most prudent?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Set their rowboats adrift and we'll at least strike a blow to their supply lines. \\n\\nHonor and duty, my friend, honor and duty!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Bravo, my bold friend! I feared the pirates would overwhelm you, but it seems you are nigh unstoppable. \\n\\nWith their supplies cut off and boats adrift, their ability to wage war will be severely diminished.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "A Pirate's Plan",
        "Description": "Grace O'Malley knows what's summoning the Lost. Go into the Pirates' den and destroy the evil artifact.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She's not a spy. She's on our side.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "She insisted she was here scouting the place for her own ends. \\n\\nI find that extremely hard to believe. Look at her, looking all suspicious. But I suppose if you're willing to vouch for her, we should at least hear what she has to say.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Charging into the pirates' compound could very well be a foolhardy notion. \\n\\nI trust your judgment, however.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "No surprise there. Miss O'Malley gets what she wants and disappears. \\n\\nI do hope your courage accomplished more than padding her coin purse.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Knight's Vigil",
        "Description": "Ser Payne Bennett has asked you to use the Spirit Shrine to get to Prydwen quickly and warn the Regent about the Lost Pirates.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, it was calling the Lost.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Interesting. Perhaps that's why we're seeing even fewer of the scoundrels coming ashore than before. \\n\\nThis revelation should be taken back to the Knight-Regent with all haste!",
        "InProgressResponse": "I’ll stay here to contain these foul brigands. \\n\\nYou take word to the Knight-Regent. Good fortune to you, my stalwart friend!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It is most excellent to see you return in good health. You are one of the few I can trust in these strange times. \\n\\nYour… enterprising friend Grace left just moments ago. She said some foul altar was rallying the pirates?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 13,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "A Matter of Discretion",
        "Description": "Regent Jin Jae has asked you to follow up on Younge Geiser's findings about the tablet and the altar. He's her resident expert on the Ancients.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is that where the Lost came from?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Many have sought answers to such questions, but few can claim to have reliable knowledge. \\n\\nOne thing I do know however, is that the Lost usually stay away from the ruins of the Ancients.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Please exercise discretion in speaking of these matters around town. \\n\\nThe people are excited about the Heir's return; I would not dampen their spirits.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There you are! I started to venture into those ruins after you, but I lost my nerve when I caught sight of those Guardians. \\n\\nI hope you found something in there to make it worth your while.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_17",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Minister Lochnir's Mission",
        "Description": "Grace witnessed Lochnir rallying the townsfolk of Prydwen to head south and welcome the True Heir. Answers to his true motives lie somewhere in these ruins.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He's planning something bad.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'd say there's no doubt about that! I tailed the bastard and his entourage. They marched straight into a crowd of the Lost. \\n\\nThe Knight-Regent says Lochnir's gone mad. She wants you to come help as soon as you're done here.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Whatever that Minister Lochnir's up to, it's well scary. \\n\\nI'd say let's finish our work here as quick as we can and get going.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, you were gone long enough, I was starting to worry you'd fallen to those Guardians. \\n\\nDid you find anything else in there relating to the Minister's plans?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_18",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "The True Threat",
        "Description": "Grace O'Malley has asked you to share the truth about Lochnir with the Knight-Regent at Preiddeu Farms.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She left the town unprotected?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "She left Ser Payne in charge of Prydwen's defenses. She wanted to see to these troubles personally. \\n\\nI suspect the Knight-Regent's looking to draw steel against Lochnir herself. You best get going.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Keep your eyes on the horizon, my friend, and always stay upwind of your enemies.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well met, stranger. The Knight-Regent said you have been her only reliable counsel in recent days. \\n\\nFor your service to her, and to Prydwen, I salute you. I was a knight myself, not long ago.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Heavy Lies the Crown",
        "Description": "Percilla Wallen suspects it's already too late, but you could try to recover the Circlet Of Swords from Teyrnon Keep.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, he can control the Lost.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That… explains much. I know the Minister had planned to claim the Circlet of Swords, the royal crown of Monarch's Bluffs, from Teyrnon Keep. \\n\\nIf he can control the Lost Knights there, I suppose that's how he'll do it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Again, I would urge you to reconsider this course of action. \\n\\nMy fellow knights are formidable combatants. Getting their seals will be difficult.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You ventured into Teyrnon Keep and returned with your soul intact? You are indeed as worthy as the Knight-Regent claimed. \\n\\nI trust you discovered that Lochnir had already taken the crown? I suspected as much.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_MB_Grace_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Southern Scout",
        "Description": "Percilla Wallen has advised you meet Grace and stay informed of her latest findings at Deadman's Shrine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Minister reminded us of our sworn duty to the royal bloodline. He told us the sacrifice of becoming Lost was noble and right. \\n\\nThen he lined us up, and killed us one-by one. I… faltered. I couldn't do it, so I... fled.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I believe the Knight-Regent said this new scout was a recent arrival, like yourself. \\n\\nI think her name was Grace.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thank goodness I found someone I can report to! And better it's not the Knight-Regent. \\n\\nRemember all those Lost pirates swarming around that den to the north? That was a small affair compared to this place.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "The Plot against Prydwen",
        "Description": "Stop the Lost fleet from leaving Scallywag Bay. Start with their explosives and then destroy their altar.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We have to stop them.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, we've discussed this partnership before, haven't we? I get the lay of the land, and you do the battling part. \\n\\nYou'll be facing long odds, but you're like a lucky anchor. I'd consider making a wager on you, regardless.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll be heading north, and I hope you'll follow soon. \\n\\nI look forward to hearing your stories at the Prydwen tavern.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So she spoke the truth after all? That Grace character told me you'd gone in there on your own, but I had to see it to believe it. \\n\\nI heard the ruckus and saw the smoke. Am I to assume that means your mission was a success?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Knight to Castle",
        "Description": "Percilla Wallen suspects Ser Gawain, the True Heir and Lochnir, the scheming minister, have gone to Corbenic Castle. Meet her there.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should go then.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, though we need a plan. They have the Circlet of Swords and an army of Lost has already fallen under Ser Gawain's influence. \\n\\nDefeating a knight of legend will be hard enough, but won't he just return to command them again?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Meet me at Corbenic Castle. \\n\\nWe'll put an end to all this madness!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, here we are. This is the moment of truth. \\n\\nIf we fail here, the Lost will overrun Prydwen and everyone in it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 16,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_PercillaWallen_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_23",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Lost Legacy",
        "Description": "The time of judgement is nigh. Confront Ser Gawain, the True Heir and the pestilent Minister Lochnir at Corbenic Castle.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Alright. Let's strike now.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Your courage is unquestionable, and I've witnessed your prowess in battle. You're a force to be reckoned with. \\n\\nBut if I'm being honest, I'd prefer not to take up arms against my former comrades nor the heir of Artorius.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do what must be done. \\n\\nYou're the only one who can stop them!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I think I've been holding my breath since you departed, or at least it feels that way. \\n\\nTell me, did you defeat Ser Gawain and destroy Lochnir's infernal staff?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_RegentJinJae",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "A True Leader",
        "Description": "Ser Gawain and Lochnir have been vanquished! In the absence of the True Heir, find a True Ruler for the crown.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The Knight-Regent should have it.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, though Jae is bound by her duty. She'd make an excellent queen but she can't even imagine such a thing. \\n\\nI suspect the court training of her youth is to blame. Her humility will be yet another formidable foe.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Now that we have the Circlet of Swords, we need to convince Jin Jae to take the mantle of leadership.\\n\\nHopefully, she'll accept the crown.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Word of your victory has already breached the walls, and we are extremely grateful. \\n\\nI welcome you back to Prydwen as a hero. I can never repay the debt this town owes to you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Wilderness Wiseman",
        "Description": "Meet Yonas, the fisherman at the east river. Maybe he has the answers to the voices inside your head.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So you will accept the crown?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, after careful consideration, I realize it is the honorable thing. It is the ultimate requirement of my sworn duty. \\n\\nWill you stay then and serve Prydwen at my side? Or do voices call you elsewhere?",
        "InProgressResponse": "If anyone can help you, it would be that old man. \\n\\nHe's often fishing on the river to the east. Look for him there.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Away with you, ghost. You'll scare away the fish. \\n\\nI remember you not and care not to, even if I could.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MSQ_00_init",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success_alt",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "0",
        "Title": "Wilderness Wiseman",
        "Description": "Meet Yonas, the fisherman at the east river. Maybe he has the answers to the voices inside your head.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So you will accept the crown?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, after careful consideration, I realize it is the honorable thing. It is the ultimate requirement of my sworn duty. \\n\\nWill you stay then and serve Prydwen at my side? Or do voices call you elsewhere?",
        "InProgressResponse": "If anyone can help you, it would be that old man. \\n\\nHe's often fishing on the river to the east. Look for him there.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Away with you, ghost. You'll scare away the fish. \\n\\nI remember you not and care not to, even if I could.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_FionaMurphy",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Flowers for the Heir",
        "Description": "The True Heir is returning to Monarch's Bluffs! Fiona Murphy has asked you to bring Avalon Lilies to Pendragon Landing as a tribute.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“They sound important.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Mountain and dale speak the tale, a warrior of wit and renown. \\n\\nArtorius raised them strong and brave, a True Heir for his crown.",
        "InProgressResponse": "No tribute too large, no deed too small, when the fated ship comes home. \\n\\nLay down a carpet of flowers, all, for when the True Heir takes the throne.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The True Heir sought to save us once, and now, the answer they’ll bring. \\n\\nThe Lost will learn, be forever turned. They’ll know them as Our One True King!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_EddaYonkers",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "The Anniversary Gift",
        "Description": "Edda Koning wants you to remind her husband, Eddie Koning it's their anniversary. Carry the message to Cynefin Mine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Were you expecting him?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, my foolish heart can't help long for my Eddie. He toils too hard in the mines. \\n\\nThis is the first time he’s missed our anniversary! I’d go to the mines myself but his favorite turkey is roasting away.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you find my Eddie yet? \\n\\nAsk him to stop working and get here quickly!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh dear, he’s not with you. That can only mean… He wrote a letter? He hates writing! \\n\\nBlast that domkop! He loves me so much. I-I- told him to stay with me. But, no! He had to go to the mines and pick at another rock.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Pick of the Mines",
        "Description": "Prydwen is short on resources. Cemal, the Master Builder has asked you to retrieve the miners' picks so that he may melt them into iron.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I can retrieve the picks.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Would you? That would be a big help! \\n\\nYou can tell Foreman Allya I'll get her more picks, and better ones too, once more iron comes in.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you get all the miners' picks? \\n\\nWe need all the iron we can get!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "…8, 9, 10. The miners' picks are all here, all accounted for and in good condition. \\n\\nThis will be a big aid to building our defenses. How can I thank you for this?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_AsheDubois_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_12",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Blow 'Em Down!",
        "Description": "Squire Ashe needs your help to blow up a bunch of pirates at Brysedd Shore.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“When did you come to the island?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I was a baby. And an absolute terror. Folks here say I used to leap out from behind trees and startle them. \\n\\nMy bag had a fleur-de-lis. And I spoke a little French back then.",
        "InProgressResponse": "What are you waiting for? \\n\\nBlow up the pirates, already!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hah! That was magnifique! You’re handy with gunpowder barrels! \\n\\nSer Payne said he might even make you a squire!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 11,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_HugoMolina",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "A Wife's Mirror",
        "Description": "A wistful Hugo Molina has asked you to help him find the missing fragments of his Lost wife's mirror.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Is eternal life that bad?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It is when you’re the reason your woman is no more. Even the moon burns you. Fatimah’s soul gave up on me. \\n\\nShe came to me in a dream the other day and asked me to piece together this mirror. But I don’t have all the fragments.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you have any luck with the missing fragments of Fatimah's mirror? \\n\\nShe hasn't asked for much and I wish to give it to her, if I possibly can.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Gracias, kind soul! Fatimah always loved her mirrors. With this last fragment, she can have her final one. \\n\\nShe said mirrors have a certain magic to them. And I can sense the energy in this, almost a strange calling…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_06_GatherJewels",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 11,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_OldeGeiser",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_06_GatherJewels_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "An Olde Tale",
        "Description": "Help Olde Geiser provide the families of the Lost with some peace. Collect Crystalline Tears and Glittering Stones for him to build memorials with.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What's your new calling?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I craft Lost memorials from Crystalline Tears, to soothe grieving families. \\n\\nPeace is always in demand. Many ask me for my services. But, the Crystalline Tears are over and so, the tears of people must wait.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did the ruins reveal their secrets and shed their tears for you? \\n\\nNot yet? Well, may your sight be sharp and your pick be purposeful.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "So many tears, such little time. You've done well by bringing these Crystalline Tears. \\n\\nYou will be in the thoughts of many families when they say the final prayers for their kin.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_JeongNabi",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "The Maidens Lost",
        "Description": "Nabi has asked for evidence to prove getting married is not the answer to turning Lost. Hopefully, this will get her meddlesome marriage-minded mother off her back.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“You've always been royal?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes. Once upon a time, I was even destined to be queen. But I lost my betrothed to the sea on our way to the island.\\n\\nMy mother hasn't given up hope I will be married one day. She fears the worst if I don't.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you find any items that show some of the Lost used to be married once? \\n\\nMy mother spoke of a dashing young man called Elias, and while I'm sure he's delightful, I simply have no aspirations to be married!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "A talisman? To protect me from evil and lower my chances of turning into a ghost? \\n\\nDoes this mean my mother no longer believes marrying is protection against turning into the Lost?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 12,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_HamzaKillic",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Dentistry Artistry",
        "Description": "Hamza Killic's brain is dancing with a new idea. Collect wolf fangs so that he may bring his invention to life!",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“How long have you been here?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "More days than a snail has teeth. I left to pursue my great ideas in my reckless youth. \\n\\nI still feel as reckless and almost as young. And if I can get enough wolf teeth, I'll finally be able to craft my invention!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you get the six wolf teeth like I asked? \\n\\nI’ll be able to complete my brilliant invention then. Trust me, you've never seen anything as daring as this!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You spotted the wolves well - middle-aged, strong, aggressive fighters most likely.  \\n\\nThese are the perfect fangs. They're sparkly. They're white. They can cut through meat!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_OliviaBarovier",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Heart of Glass",
        "Description": "A grieving Olivia Barovier has asked you to retrieve her Lost father's glassworks from Arruda Ranch.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What demons?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Scars. My father's mistakes wore him down till he broke. He always thought the world was better... He shattered when he saw the truth. \\n\\nHe lost himself in making glassworks. People came from all over the island to buy them.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Were you able to enter the house? \\n\\nDid you find my father’s glassworks?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Getting into the house must not have been easy. I am grateful for your courage. \\n\\nThese are the last things I have of my father. At least he got to spend his last days with his precious work.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 14,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_HugoMolina_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Ending the Madness",
        "Description": "Fixing the mirror for Hugo worsened matters. He needs your help breaking the large mirror at Deadman's Cove, so that he can finally let go of his Lost wife.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Have you tried breaking it?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I had to. Her words are still pounding in my head. \\n\\nI broke her heart. And now I've broken her mirror. Maybe that's why she won't stop haunting me.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Were you able to destroy the mirror or did Fatimah's voice get to you too? \\n\\nMy Fatimah can be quite compelling.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "How is it that you can love someone and yet living with them can slowly destroy you? \\n\\nThis island didn’t help. But oh, Fatimah, I miss you so much.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 15,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_DayoMusa",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "A Useless Hope",
        "Description": "Dayo Musa's hopeful plan went horribly wrong. Retrieve the amulets from the Lost to put them at ease and return the amulets to him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "(Keep reading)",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I tried to guide the people towards their faith, by giving them something tangible to focus on. \\n\\nI made sure each of them had an amulet to see them through. Like the stories of old, we’d weather this plague together.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The journals of Dayo Musa should really be discussed with him.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hello, friend! I hope this day is treating you with kindness. \\n\\nWould you have time to help a fellow? Regrettably, the people I was trying to protect have turned into the Lost…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_AsheDubois",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_21 \u0026\u0026 12A_Side_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Knight? Who? Me?",
        "Description": "Ashe Dubois, Ser Payne's squire, has always longed to be a knight. Give her the proof that someone in her family used to be a knight once.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "(Keep reading)",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The helm, the bow, and the crest of Margot will mark the Dubois family history. \\n\\nThrough generations, the Dubois name will be welcome in the halls of Artorius. They must be informed that they can uphold this honor.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The proclamation concerning the Dubois Family Crest should should be taken to Ashe Dubois.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Really? You found something that belonged to my family! \\n\\nWhat is it? Who are they? Where can I meet them?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_GeertieLother",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_13",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Devil Honey",
        "Description": "Get combs of Devil's Honey from Geertie Lother's private reserve at Hiraeth Lookout and return them to her in Prydwen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do people say, exactly?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "They say you've been quite a help, and I was like, \"Well, why haven't they helped me?\" \\n\\nBut then I realized, silly Geertie, it's because you haven't asked!",
        "InProgressResponse": "You’ll find the honeycombs at Hiraeth Lookout. \\n\\nJust wait until you taste this honey!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Aha! There's my honey! Er, I mean my honeycombs. I wasn't calling you \"my honey.\" That would be... absurd. \\n\\nBut yes, this is fantastic! I'm going to whip us up some honeycakes right away.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 9,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_GeertieLother",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_14",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_13",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "1",
        "Title": "Old World Wine",
        "Description": "Celebrate while you still can. Collect jars of Old World wine from Brysedd Shore and share them with Geertie Lother!",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Depends on the favor.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Seeing as how everyone is talking about \"battening down the hatches\" here to protect against the Lost, I think we need to stock up on spirits. \\n\\nAnd I think I might know a spot to get our hands on some perfectly aged wine from the Old World.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Stars above! The Old World wine from Brysedd Shore! I can't wait. \\n\\nPirates sure have all the best stuff!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh yeah, I can feel the party coming on already! \\n\\nWe got wine and honeycakes - it's gonna be a feast!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_15",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "Resources for Prydwen",
        "Description": "Collect Stone, Wood and Leather for Cemal Qadir, Prydwen's Master Builder, so that he can build good defenses for Prydwen.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Why would you say that?”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, I've run into some supply troubles. I was expecting a shipment of stone, timber, and leather this week. \\n\\nNothing’s turned up yet. I fear the poor souls I found to help me may have turned into the Lost.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you get everything? Not one hair of leather should be missing.  \\n\\nEvery resource counts towards fortifying Prydwen’s defenses.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Great! You brought exactly what I needed, the right type and the right amount. \\n\\nWere you always this resourceful?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_CemalQadir",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_15",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "A Sword for a Friend",
        "Description": "Cemal Qadir is very happy with the work you've done and wants to do something for you in turn. Learn how to build a sword with his guidance.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“One good turn deserves another.”",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Words to live by, rajal sadaq! You could be knight material and I want to see you make it through a few more summers, at least. \\n\\nHas anyone taught you how to make a sword?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Craft me the best sword you can! \\n\\nI want to see what you’re capable of!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "That's a fine-looking sword, rajal sadaq. It would almost rival the swords in Syria. \\n\\nI'm not surprised. It’s what I've come to expect from you.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 7,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "12A_Side_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "12A_Side_16",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": "FALSE",
        "Title": "The Town Project Board",
        "Description": "Visit the Town Project Board of Monarch's Bluffs and find tasks to help the people of the settlement.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
